

CHRISTIAN NGUBANA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a software developer with a strong passion for problem-solving. I enjoy building software products that not only meet organizational needs but also elevate user experiences. I care about writing high-quality software that delivers bespoke products and services.

CONTACT

- Cape Town, South Africa 7460
- christian1.raymond@gmail.com
- ₩ebsite
- in <u>LinkedIn</u>
- GitHub

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ••• HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript/ES6+
- • • ReactJS/ReduxJS/TailwindCSS
- Docker/ExpressJS/NextJS/MUI
- ●●●● NodeJS/MySQL/MongoDB/SQL
- •••• Monday.com/CI,CD/JiraCloud
- ●●● Bootstrap/Git/RESTful API's

SOFT SKILLS

- Time Management / Team work
 / Excellent communication
 skills
- Critical thinking & Problem Solving / Public speaking
- Adaptability / Self starting & Mentoring

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer

Injozi Digital | Jan 2023 - Present, Remote

Responsible for turning wireframes and mock-ups into reusable code and building high-quality UI components, and scalability. Develop features with web development best practices.

Collaborate with teams and stakeholders across the organization to discuss the needs, design, and functionality of the project. Debug errors, troubleshoot issues, and perform routine performance optimizations.

Frontend Developer Platform45 | Nov 2021 - Oct 2022

Helped my team develop high-quality software.

Built beautifully designed digital products for both international and local clients, optimized UI/UX processes, and accessible across a broad range of platforms.

Identified areas for modification in existing programs and subsequently developed these modifications, consulted and worked closely with crossfunctional teams to gather requirements.

EDUCATION HISTORY

CS50 | Harvard University | May 2019 CodeX - Software Engineering Studies | Feb 2017 - Jan 2018 Together Technologies Bootcamp - Web Development | South Africa - 2016 CPUT | Cape Town South Africa - Civil Engineering | 2014 - Dropout

References

Jeremy Ramos: Senior lead Engineer at Platform45 jeremy@platform45.com: +27 78 642 5850

Thato Maloka: Senior Engineer manager at Injozi Digital thato@injozi.biz: +27 73 954 8248

Greg van Berkel: CEO at Code at Collective greg@codecollective.com: +27 84 473 4679